[
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a function of the kidneys?",
        "options": ["Regulation of blood pressure", "Excretion of waste products", "Hormone production", "All of the above"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "F", "T"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which component is not included in a Basic Metabolic Panel (BMP)?",
        "options": ["Sodium", "Glucose", "Bilirubin", "Calcium"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "T", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Elevated blood urea nitrogen (BUN) levels can indicate:",
        "options": ["Kidney dysfunction", "Dehydration", "High protein diet", "All of the above"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "F", "T"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following substances is primarily excreted by the kidneys?",
        "options": ["Creatinine", "Bilirubin", "Hemoglobin", "Ammonia"],
        "answer": ["T", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "The eGFR test is used to measure:",
        "options": ["Liver function", "Blood glucose levels", "Kidney function", "Heart function"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "T", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "The primary purpose of a laboratory test for diagnosis is to:",
        "options": ["Monitor drug therapy", "Rule in or rule out a diagnosis", "Screen for congenital conditions", "Conduct research"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Clinical laboratory tests do not include:",
        "options": ["General chemistry", "Clinical endocrinology", "Electrophysiology", "Toxicology"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "T", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which test is not included in a Comprehensive Metabolic Panel (CMP)?",
        "options": ["Sodium", "Calcium", "Albumin", "Glucose"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "A lipid profile test measures:",
        "options": ["Kidney function", "Liver enzymes", "Blood lipid levels", "Hormone levels"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "T", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which marker is used to detect myocardial infarction?",
        "options": ["Troponin", "Creatinine", "Bilirubin", "Albumin"],
        "answer": ["T", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which amino acid is not essential?",
        "options": ["Leucine", "Valine", "Methionine", "Glutamine"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "F", "T"]
    },
    {
        "question": "The liver is primarily responsible for the synthesis of which type of protein?",
        "options": ["Plasma proteins", "Enzymes", "Hormones", "Membrane proteins"],
        "answer": ["T", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Serum albumin is classified as a:",
        "options": ["Conjugated protein", "Simple protein", "Derived protein", "Metalloprotein"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which immunoglobulin provides immunity to the fetus?",
        "options": ["IgA", "IgG", "IgM", "IgE"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which technique separates plasma proteins by electrical charge?",
        "options": ["Ultracentrifugation", "Immunologic analysis", "Electrophoresis", "Enzymatic digestion"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "T", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "The best indicator of kidney function is:",
        "options": ["Blood urea nitrogen (BUN)", "Serum creatinine", "Estimated glomerular filtration rate (eGFR)", "Urine protein levels"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "T", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What should be considered before ordering a laboratory test?",
        "options": ["Cost of the test", "Interpretation of the results", "Reliability of the test", "Purpose of the test"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "F", "T"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which function is not performed by plasma proteins?",
        "options": ["Oncotic pressure regulation", "Enzyme activity", "Immune response", "DNA replication"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "F", "T"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Essential amino acids cannot be synthesized by the body and must be supplied through food. Which of the following is an essential amino acid?",
        "options": ["Leucine", "Glycine", "Alanine", "Proline", "Tyrosine"],
        "answer": ["T", "F", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following statements is true regarding plasma proteins compared to tissue proteins?",
        "options": ["Plasma proteins have a higher carbohydrate content.", "Plasma proteins have less -S-S- bonds than intra-cellular proteins.", "Tissue proteins are more soluble than plasma proteins.", "Tissue proteins are typically glycoproteins.", "Plasma proteins are less prone to denaturation."],
        "answer": ["T", "F", "T", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the primary site for the catabolism of proteins in the body?",
        "options": ["Kidney", "Liver", "Intestine", "Stomach", "Pancreas"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which method is NOT used for assessing plasma protein concentration?",
        "options": ["Ultracentrifugation", "Immunologic analysis", "X-ray diffraction", "Electrophoresis", "Spectrophotometry"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "T", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which immunoglobulin is responsible for protection of mucosal surfaces?",
        "options": ["IgG", "IgA", "IgM", "IgE", "IgD"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following plasma proteins is involved in blood clotting?",
        "options": ["Albumin", "Fibrinogen", "Immunoglobulin", "Transferrin", "Ceruloplasmin"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following conditions is characterized by hyposecretion of gastric juice?",
        "options": ["Peptic ulcer disease", "Zollinger-Ellison syndrome", "Pernicious anemia", "Chronic gastritis", "Crohn's disease"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "T", "T", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Pentagastrin Secretion Test, what is the normal basal acid output for males?",
        "options": ["0-5 mmol/hr", "0-10.5 mmol/hr", "5-15 mmol/hr", "15-20 mmol/hr", "20-25 mmol/hr"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which enzyme is more specific for the pancreas and can be useful to measure if the source of a raised plasma amylase is not obvious?",
        "options": ["Trypsin", "Elastase", "Chymotrypsin", "Amylase", "Lipase"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "F", "F", "T"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is indicated by a low urinary excretion of p-aminobenzoic acid (PABA) in the PABA test for chymotrypsin?",
        "options": ["Normal pancreatic function", "Chronic pancreatitis", "Renal dysfunction", "Liver disease", "Malabsorption"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "T", "T", "T"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which condition is not a cause of low vitamin B12 absorption indicated by the Schilling test?",
        "options": ["Lack of intrinsic factor", "Small bowel bacterial overgrowth", "Gastrectomy", "Cystic fibrosis", "Pancreatic enzyme deficiency"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "F", "T", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What diagnostic approach is used to identify lactose intolerance?",
        "options": ["Pentagastrin Secretion Test", "Schilling Test", "Hydrogen Breath Test", "Lundh Test Meal", "Tubation Method"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "T", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first step in bilirubin metabolism?",
        "options": ["Production", "Uptake by the hepatocyte", "Conjugation", "Excretion into bile ducts", "Delivery to the intestine"],
        "answer": ["T", "F", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which enzyme is involved in the conjugation of bilirubin?",
        "options": ["UDP-glucuronosyltransferase", "Heme oxygenase", "Biliverdin reductase", "Bilirubin oxidase", "Cytochrome P450"],
        "answer": ["T", "F", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In which organ does the conjugation of bilirubin primarily occur?",
        "options": ["Liver", "Kidney", "Spleen", "Bone Marrow", "Intestine"],
        "answer": ["T", "F", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the primary product of heme catabolism?",
        "options": ["Biliverdin", "Bilirubin", "Iron", "Carbon monoxide", "Hemosiderin"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which compound is responsible for the yellow color of jaundice?",
        "options": ["Bilirubin", "Biliverdin", "Heme", "Iron", "Albumin"],
        "answer": ["T", "F", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which condition is characterized by high levels of unconjugated bilirubin in the blood?",
        "options": ["Hemolytic anemia", "Gilbert's syndrome", "Cirrhosis", "Dubin-Johnson syndrome", "Crigler-Najjar syndrome"],
        "answer": ["T", "T", "F", "F", "T"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main transport protein for bilirubin in the blood?",
        "options": ["Albumin", "Hemoglobin", "Transferrin", "Ferritin", "Ceruloplasmin"],
        "answer": ["T", "F", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which form of bilirubin is water-soluble?",
        "options": ["Conjugated bilirubin", "Unconjugated bilirubin", "Biliverdin", "Protoporphyrin", "Urobilinogen"],
        "answer": ["T", "F", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Where does the excretion of conjugated bilirubin into bile occur?",
        "options": ["Bile ducts", "Kidney", "Spleen", "Bone Marrow", "Liver sinusoids"],
        "answer": ["T", "F", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which molecule is a precursor to bilirubin?",
        "options": ["Heme", "Hemoglobin", "Iron", "Myoglobin", "Cytochrome"],
        "answer": ["T", "T", "F", "T", "T"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hormone decreases blood glucose levels by increasing glycolysis, glycogenesis, and lipogenesis?",
        "options": ["Insulin", "Glucagon", "Adrenalin", "Cortisol", "Growth Hormone"],
        "answer": ["T", "F", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the primary cause of hyperglycemia in diabetes mellitus?",
        "options": ["Excess insulin secretion", "Defects in insulin secretion or action", "Excess glycogen storage", "Overactive glycolysis", "Increased lipogenesis"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a symptom of diabetes mellitus?",
        "options": ["Fatigue", "Nausea", "Frequent urination", "Thirst", "Increased weight gain"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "F", "F", "T"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which enzyme deficiency leads to severe hypoglycemia and is treated by removing fructose from the diet?",
        "options": ["Hexokinase", "Aldolase B", "Galactokinase", "Pyruvate Dehydrogenase", "Glucose-6-Phosphate Dehydrogenase"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which condition is characterized by the inability to convert galactose to glucose and can lead to infantile cataracts?",
        "options": ["Congenital Fructose Intolerance", "Galactosemia", "Pyruvate Dehydrogenase Deficiency", "Glycogen Storage Disease", "G6PD Deficiency"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hormone increases blood glucose by promoting glycogenolysis and gluconeogenesis?",
        "options": ["Insulin", "Glucagon", "Cortisol", "Thyroxine", "Somatostatin"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the central molecule in carbohydrate metabolism?",
        "options": ["Fructose", "Sucrose", "Lactose", "Glucose", "Galactose"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "F", "T", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which disorder is characterized by persistent hyperglycemia and disturbances of carbohydrate, fat, and protein metabolism?",
        "options": ["Hypoglycemia", "Diabetes Mellitus", "Glycogen Storage Disease", "Galactosemia", "Pyruvate Dehydrogenase Deficiency"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of inheritance pattern is observed in most inborn errors of carbohydrate metabolism?",
        "options": ["Autosomal Dominant", "X-Linked Recessive", "Autosomal Recessive", "Mitochondrial", "Y-Linked"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "T", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following can trigger hemolytic anemia in individuals with G6PD deficiency?",
        "options": ["Primaquine", "Sulfonamides", "Aspirin", "Fava Beans", "All of the above"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "F", "F", "T"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the pH range of normal blood?",
        "options": ["6.8 - 7.2", "7.0 - 7.3", "7.35 - 7.45", "7.5 - 7.6", "7.2 - 7.4"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "T", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a volatile acid in the body?",
        "options": ["H2SO4", "HCl", "H2CO3", "Lactic acid", "Acetoacetic acid"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "T", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Henderson-Hasselbalch equation is used to calculate:",
        "options": ["pH", "HCO3-", "pCO2", "Base excess", "Buffer capacity"],
        "answer": ["T", "F", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following organs is primarily responsible for the regulation of acid-base balance?",
        "options": ["Liver", "Kidney", "Heart", "Lungs", "Brain"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "T", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which buffer system is the most important in extracellular fluid?",
        "options": ["Hemoglobin buffer system", "Phosphate buffer system", "Protein buffer system", "Bicarbonate buffer system", "Ammonia buffer system"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "F", "T", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following can lead to metabolic acidosis?",
        "options": ["Excessive vomiting", "Diabetes mellitus", "Hyperventilation", "Excessive intake of antacids", "Renal failure"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "F", "T"]
    },
    {
        "question": "The primary response to metabolic acidosis is:",
        "options": ["Increased renal HCO3- excretion", "Decreased respiratory rate", "Increased respiratory rate", "Decreased renal HCO3- reabsorption", "Increased renal HCO3- reabsorption"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "T", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ammoniagenesis occurs in which part of the nephron?",
        "options": ["Proximal tubule", "Distal tubule", "Collecting duct", "Loop of Henle", "Glomerulus"],
        "answer": ["T", "F", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which enzyme catalyzes the formation of carbonic acid from carbon dioxide and water?",
        "options": ["Carbonic anhydrase", "Hydrogenase", "Oxidase", "Dehydrogenase", "Reductase"],
        "answer": ["T", "F", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "A decrease in pH corresponds to an increase in:",
        "options": ["HCO3- concentration", "H+ concentration", "pCO2", "Oxygen saturation", "Base excess"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "T", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is an example of a non-volatile acid?",
        "options": ["H2CO3", "HCl", "CO2", "H2SO4", "NH3"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "T", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Respiratory compensation for metabolic alkalosis involves:",
        "options": ["Hyperventilation", "Hypoventilation", "Increased renal H+ excretion", "Decreased renal HCO3- reabsorption", "Increased renal NH3 production"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "The anion gap is calculated to evaluate:",
        "options": ["Osmotic balance", "Electrolyte imbalance", "Acid-base disorders", "Renal function", "Liver function"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "T", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following acts as a buffer in the blood?",
        "options": ["Glucose", "Albumin", "Hemoglobin", "Creatinine", "Lactate"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "T", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which organ plays a major role in compensating for chronic respiratory acidosis?",
        "options": ["Liver", "Kidney", "Heart", "Lungs", "Spleen"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a function of lipids in the body?",
        "options": ["Energy storage", "Hormone production", "Insulation", "Cell membrane structure", "All of the above"],
        "answer": ["T", "T", "T", "T", "T"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a sterol derivative?",
        "options": ["Cholesterol", "Fatty acids", "Triglycerides", "Sphingomyelin", "Terpenes"],
        "answer": ["T", "F", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which organ is the primary site for cholesterol synthesis?",
        "options": ["Liver", "Kidney", "Intestine", "Adipose tissue", "Pancreas"],
        "answer": ["T", "F", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the primary function of HDL in lipid metabolism?",
        "options": ["Transport triglycerides", "Store fat", "Transport cholesterol to the liver", "Synthesize fatty acids", "Produce bile acids"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "T", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which enzyme is responsible for the esterification of cholesterol in the blood?",
        "options": ["HMG-CoA reductase", "Lipoprotein lipase", "Lecithin-cholesterol acyltransferase", "Acyl-CoA cholesterol acyltransferase", "Hormone-sensitive lipase"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "T", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which lipoprotein is known as 'bad cholesterol'?",
        "options": ["HDL", "LDL", "VLDL", "IDL", "Chylomicron"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which fatty acid is considered essential?",
        "options": ["Oleic acid", "Linoleic acid", "Stearic acid", "Palmitic acid", "Myristic acid"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which apolipoprotein is primarily found in HDL?",
        "options": ["Apo A", "Apo B100", "Apo C", "Apo E", "Apo B48"],
        "answer": ["T", "F", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a primary function of bile acids?",
        "options": ["Protein synthesis", "Fat digestion", "Carbohydrate metabolism", "Hormone regulation", "Electrolyte balance"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which lipoprotein is synthesized in the liver and primarily transports triglycerides?",
        "options": ["HDL", "LDL", "VLDL", "IDL", "Chylomicron"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "T", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a characteristic of saturated fatty acids?",
        "options": ["Contains no double bonds", "Liquid at room temperature", "Lower melting point", "Derived from plants", "Includes omega-3 fatty acids"],
        "answer": ["T", "F", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the primary function of lipoprotein lipase?",
        "options": ["Hydrolyze triglycerides in lipoproteins", "Synthesize cholesterol", "Transport fatty acids", "Activate HDL", "Inhibit lipolysis"],
        "answer": ["T", "F", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which lipoprotein has the highest triglyceride content?",
        "options": ["HDL", "LDL", "VLDL", "IDL", "Chylomicron"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "F", "F", "T"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following conditions is associated with hyperlipidemia?",
        "options": ["Atherosclerosis", "Hypothyroidism", "Diabetes mellitus", "Obesity", "All of the above"],
        "answer": ["T", "T", "T", "T", "T"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which enzyme is the rate-limiting step in cholesterol synthesis?",
        "options": ["Lecithin-cholesterol acyltransferase", "Hormone-sensitive lipase", "HMG-CoA reductase", "Lipoprotein lipase", "Acyl-CoA cholesterol acyltransferase"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "T", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What percentage of total body weight is water in adult males?",
        "options": ["30%", "40%", "50%", "60%", "70%"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "F", "T", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which compartment contains the largest percentage of body water?",
        "options": ["Intracellular fluid", "Extracellular fluid", "Plasma", "Interstitial fluid", "Transcellular fluid"],
        "answer": ["T", "F", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a major cation in the extracellular fluid?",
        "options": ["Potassium", "Sodium", "Calcium", "Magnesium", "Phosphate"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the normal range of serum osmolality?",
        "options": ["275-295 mOsm/kg", "250-270 mOsm/kg", "300-320 mOsm/kg", "220-240 mOsm/kg", "290-310 mOsm/kg"],
        "answer": ["T", "F", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hormone is primarily responsible for water reabsorption in the kidneys?",
        "options": ["Aldosterone", "Antidiuretic hormone", "Renin", "Angiotensin II", "Cortisol"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following conditions is characterized by hyponatremia?",
        "options": ["Dehydration", "Diabetes insipidus", "Syndrome of inappropriate antidiuretic hormone secretion (SIADH)", "Hyperaldosteronism", "Cushing's syndrome"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "T", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the primary stimulus for the release of aldosterone?",
        "options": ["High blood glucose", "Low blood pressure", "High blood pressure", "Low blood glucose", "Increased body temperature"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following ions is the main determinant of plasma osmolality?",
        "options": ["Potassium", "Sodium", "Calcium", "Magnesium", "Phosphate"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which electrolyte imbalance is commonly seen in patients with chronic kidney disease?",
        "options": ["Hypokalemia", "Hyperkalemia", "Hyponatremia", "Hypocalcemia", "Hypernatremia"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "T", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hormone is primarily involved in the regulation of sodium balance?",
        "options": ["Insulin", "Glucagon", "Aldosterone", "Cortisol", "Parathyroid hormone"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "T", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following mechanisms does NOT contribute to maintaining water and electrolyte balance?",
        "options": ["Thirst mechanism", "Kidney function", "Respiratory rate", "Skin perspiration", "Dietary intake"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "T", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which ion exchange is involved in the regulation of acid-base balance in the kidneys?",
        "options": ["H+ for Na+", "K+ for Cl-", "H+ for K+", "Na+ for Ca2+", "H+ for HCO3-"],
        "answer": ["T", "F", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the effect of antidiuretic hormone (ADH) on the kidneys?",
        "options": ["Increases urine output", "Decreases urine output", "Increases sodium excretion", "Decreases potassium reabsorption", "Increases calcium absorption"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "F", "F"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which electrolyte imbalance can result from excessive use of diuretics?",
        "options": ["Hypernatremia", "Hyponatremia", "Hyperkalemia", "Hypercalcemia", "Hypokalemia"],
        "answer": ["F", "T", "F", "F", "T"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which fluid compartment is referred to as the 'third space' in the context of fluid balance?",
        "options": ["Intracellular fluid", "Extracellular fluid", "Plasma", "Interstitial fluid", "Transcellular fluid"],
        "answer": ["F", "F", "F", "F", "T"]
    }
]

